-Do you even realize you’ve been  acting super weird?
-How?
-Ouch!
-Coach Kong told me you’re dropping out.
-What are you doing?
-You should be glad
-you won’t have to see me anymore.
-If I told you the truth,
-would you change your mind?
When you said you love me,
what kind of love was it?
What do you feel about me?
I...
(Sun!)
Yes, Pa?
I just came to tell you
that the toilet on the second floor is clogged.
Use the one downstairs instead.
Yes, Pa.
What about us?
Shhh!
This is not the time.
You wanna die?
Go, leave.
Uh, Sun!
Yes, Pa?
Don’t stay up late.
Yes, Pa.
I’m going to sleep now.
Yeah.
(Will you play doubles with me?)
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION,
MINISTRY OF CULTURE
So, about you dropping out…
I’m not dropping out anymore.
And also...
I’d like to play doubles with Bay again.
What about you, Bay?
Me, too.
This is what I’m talking about!
Now…
I hope you two can sync up soon.
Yes, sir.
Of course.
You’re late.
Sorry.
Just a bun and a box of shumai.
Is this worth the delivery fees?
Well, this is all I wanna eat.
Why are you complaining?
You didn’t have to deliver it yourself.
Just pay.
Hurry.
Hey, about the other day at the hospital…
What you asked me…
Mmm.
The principal had Bay and Sun
compete in PREM’S GAME.
Like…together.
Doubles?
Uh-huh.
And…they both agreed.
That’s good.
Uh-huh.
But...
I think we should…
help each other...
keep this from you dad.
I can understand that.
If the parents find out about this,
the boys will feel pressured again.
But they have to practice together, right?
How could we keep this a secret?
The principal gave us a budget
for the kids to go practice out of town.
Are you...
interested in...
coming along to help me babysit?
Babysit?
Well…
these kids aren’t easy to handle.
If I had someone to help me,
that’d be great.
To take care of you?
Yes, to take care of me…
No, I mean the kids!
Will you come?
Please?
If I have to go alone,
it’ll be so hard for me.
Aren’t you worried about me?
Fine, I’ll go.
Yes!
This way Bay will have an excuse
to go out of town.
Great.
Thank you so much.
I’ll send you the details via LINE.
You still use the same account, right?
Mmm.
Text me.
I’ll go then.
See you.
Drive safely.
And check your LINE.
Hey!
Hey.
What are you doing?!
You’re early today.
What’s the matter with you?
Are you sick?
No.
He’s been sitting like this for 15 minutes.
Eh?
If you’re not sick, get up and go warm up.
Go.
Get up now.
Go on.
-Hey!
Are you okay?
Sun?
What’s wrong with you?
If someone confessed they liked you,
what would you do?
Who confessed?
I barely see you talk to anyone.
Hmm.
If I liked them,
I’d say ‘yes’, if not I’d just say ‘no’.
Yeah, right.
What if you don’t know if you like them or not?
Just say ‘no’ then!
Because if you liked them,
you would know.
Hey, are you crazy?!
How could I just say ‘no’?
It’s like I’m missing out on an opportunity,
right?
If you’re not feeling it,
that means you don’t like them.
Period.
What if you think you do,
but the voice in your head says
“This is not possible.”?
I can’t decide for you.
If you choose to date them and it works out,
I’m happy for you.
But if you know from the jump
that it’s not possible,
it’ll be better if you don’t start it at all.
Holy cow!
This kind of thing takes time.
You have to really get to know each other
before you decide
if they’re right for you.
You think so, Zippo?!
I know so, brother.
Just let them in.
If you like them,
everything will become possible.
Really?
-Really.
-But...
What if I realize later that I don’t like them?
Then just call it quits.
Period.
I’m not asking you for advice anymore, Keaw.
From now on
I will only talk to my boy Zippo.
Best bro forever!
Hey!
If you already had the answer,
why would you even ask me?
I didn’t have the answer.
You did.
I didn’t.
Did!
Didn’t!
-Please, the audacity!
-I didn’t!
-Enough!
-I didn’t.
Just go practice!
Go!
I didn’t.
I said go practice!
-Best bro.
-Keaw!
I can’t with him!
-I can’t with him!
Hey, Bay.
Why didn’t you come to practice today?
I had to help Petong with his portfolio.
Right.
Are you two gonna compete again
over how to get home?
I see.
Don’t even say a thing.
Nah…
I see.
Oh…
I have to go meet Minami’s brother today.
We wanted to talk it out.
I’ll see you later.
Yeah.
You go.
You two get home safe.
Yeah, yeah. We can go home by ourselves.
-Get it, bro, get it!
-Just go.
Yeah, go.
You can do it.
Yeah.
-I’ll go, bye.
-See you.
Since there’s no winner today,
wanna go home together?
Come on.
Is this yours, Sun?
Yes, Pa.
It’s for me.
Oh, you…
Are you sure you don’t want me
to drive you?
It’s okay, Pa.
I called a ride.
Before you do anything dangerous,
think about your Pa.
Why would you say that, Pa?
Well…
I’ve seen on the news
that some kids who went to the beach
died from drowning.
Think about me before you decide
to go into deep water.
Okay, Pa.
Don’t worry.
I’ll only go knee-deep into the water.
Good.
Goodbye, Pa.
Chun!
Your feng shui mirror is reflecting
toward my restaurant.
Do you want to blind my customers?
Remove it!
They said this mirror helps reflect evil energy.
Apparently, it’s working.
It’s really working.
Hey, you bastard.
-Hey!
-What?
You’re causing trouble for other people.
You should have some common sense, Chun.
So? So what?!
If you have a problem, just move away!
You asshole.
That way people won’t have to hear you
yelling or bragging about your son,
or whatever nonsense you do.
Oh, so you’re jealous?
To see that my sons are successful.
Unlike yours, who got removed from
the tennis tryout.
Hey…
Don’t talk about my son!
And what, huh?
You want it? I warned you!
Pa, that’s enough.
Come on then.
Come on!
I’m waiting.
You’re lucky my son’s holding me back.
For my son’s sake…
That’s enough, Pa.
You’re so hotheaded, huh?
You are hotheaded!
Don’t…
Don’t you come one step closer.
Oh, come on. Come to me, Chun.
I’m already here.
Bring it on.
CHARTERED BUS
Good morning.
Good morning, teacher.
“Good morning, teacher”?
Get to your seat.
I can’t with you guys.
Where are you gonna sit?
Morning, Coach.
Morning.
Hey.
You’re coming, too?
I asked Boat to help me look after
you guys.
You kids are so chaotic
I can’t watch you all by myself.
Go find your seat.
Good morning.
Good morning, Coach.
-Good morning.
Go get a seat.
Good morning, guys.
Is this all?
What’s up, Sun?
-Hi.
-We’re missing one person.
Petong.
I’m here.
-Hello.
-Good morning, Coach.
Good morning.
-Sit down.
-Morning, guys.
Scoot over.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I have no idea.
Since everyone’s going,
I wanted to go, too.
Let’s go!
Start rolling.
Door closing.
I got the keycards.
Where are Ally and Keaw?
Having a photoshoot.
Photoshoot?
I’ll get the memory full already.
I got your keycards, Ally and Keaw.
Let’s go.
They’re not playing.
Here’s your keycard.
You two stay together.
Okay.
You stay with Coach Kong then.
Old men stick together, right?
Your dad is old!
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
We share the same dad.
Don’t you remember?
He’s the only old one.
I’m not old yet.
You’re old, too.
Just kidding, Coach.
Then I’ll stay with…
I’m staying with Zippo.
Is that so?
Your keycard.
Thank you, Coach.
So Bay, you…
stay with Petong, okay?
Your keycard.
Now, everyone go unpack.
See you in half an hour.
Better start practicing soon
since we don’t have much time today.
Yes, Coach.
If you’re late, we won’t have time
to play in the water.
Okay, coming.
It’s good you’re staying with me.
It’s gonna be a long night.
Let’s go.
Now, kids,
you’re ready?
Yes!
Good.
Zippo!
Yes?
Aren’t you joining PREM’S GAME?
What?
I’m competing, too?
Haven’t I told you
I wanted you to take Sun’s place
in PREM’S GAME?
Uhh, you haven’t.
Well…
Congratulations!
Zippo will play singles in PREM’S GAME!
Yes!
I get to compete, too, Ally.
Sun. Keaw.
Go, get ready.
Go.
Good.
Go lower.
Please move.
What is this, sir?
Yes, nice. Good job.
Well done.
Focus!
Ally.
Hmm?
Do you think they are…
Oh, I clocked it.
What’s up with you two today?
You’re not in sync at all.
It’s nothing, Coach.
I just have a lot on my mind.
Sun.
What you said the other day…
It was about Bay, right?
Hey.
You can tell?
Even I can tell.
Why don’t you just talk it out?
Didn’t you say it yourself?
If you don’t think it’s possible,
why bother starting it?
Hey.
You’re playing together but you’re not talking?
We only talk about the game.
I can be professional.
If you really care about him,
you should talk to him.
How can I?
Boat is on this trip, too.
What would I do if he told his dad?
Just find the right moment.
They’re not together all the time.
Just try.
Have the talk.
Don’t you look so proud?
They’re my trainees.
How do you feel about playing tennis
with Sun again?
Actually, it was great when we
were practicing at first.
But I guess I’m the one who messed it up.
What did you do?
I might have crossed the line.
I deserve to be hated.
Can we talk?
Then talk.
What’s up with you?
Why are you here alone?
What’s going on with you?
You’ve been avoiding me all day.
Well, I don’t know how to act.
I don’t even know how I feel.
All I know is I’m not mad at you.
I’m so glad I get to play with you again.
You’re glad?
Then why are you acting like this?
Because Boat is here, too.
What if he tells your dad?
Boat knows I like you.
And he’s fine with that?
He is.
And even if he weren’t,
I wouldn’t care.
It’s that easy for you, huh?
It’s not easy.
But when I like someone,
I’m willing to give it my all.
But do you really think this is possible?
Do you like me, Sun?
If you like me too,
I’m willing to get through any obstacle.
I don’t know.
I’m still not sure.
It feels great…
knowing that you like me.
But does this mean I like you too?
I’m still not sure.
Then…
will you let me try to win you over
until you’re sure about your feelings?
♪ Ever since that day ♪
♪ When you and I happened to meet ♪
♪ It’s like a dream ♪
♪ ’Cause you’re the one ♪
♪ Who came along and made my heart skip a beat ♪
♪ It feels like I’ve finally found love ♪
You can try.
There!
You said it!
You’ll let me?!
Quiet. People will…
-Woohoo!!
-They will hear you.
I’m allowed to make a move on you!
Bay!
Woohoo!
I’ll make a move on you every second.
Keep it down.
Woohoo!
Bay!
People are staring.
-Be quiet!
-Sun!
I’ll keep trying until I can make you
my boyfriend.
-You hear that?!
-Damn it.
-They’re all looking at us.
-Sun!
Woohoo!
Keep it down!
I’ll keep trying every second.
Bay, keep it down!
Hey.
Morning, my tofu.
These remind me of back then.
Do you still remember
when we were young,
I beat you in running every time.
It was just a warm-up run.
Who takes it as a competition?
A loss is a loss.
I’ll beat you today then.
Well, you can try.
Hey! Wait up!
Hey! Wait!
Hey! Sun!
-Oops.
-Hey.
Hey! Hold on.
What?
You haven’t been working out at all,
have you?
I only need these for sculpting.
You go on.
I’ll wait here.
Just come get me later.
No way.
Come on.
I’m too tired.
Hey!
Come on.
Let’s keep running.
Okay, keep running.
Come on.
Take this!
Here.
There.
Here we go.
It’s happening.
I’ll keep my fingers crossed for
this year’s PREM’S GAME.
Aren’t you keeping your fingers crossed
for the singles as well?
I am.
But for a different reason.
Oh.
different reason.
Don’t hold back.
I’m here to support you.
Your shoelaces.
You’re just his tennis partner.
Do you have to take such good care of him?
I beat him at running this morning.
We made a deal that
the loser had to be the other’s servant.
Yeah.
I shouldn’t have lost.
Now I have to be your servant for five or ten years, or…
Bay!
Now that Bay is your servant,
what do you call him?
‘Bay-bae’.
-Or ‘Baby’.
-Zip it, Zippo.
You are…
quite a good teacher.
What?
I didn’t do anything.
You make the kids happy.
That’s good enough.
Those teachers at my school
could never be like you.
If studying medicine makes you
suffer and stressed out,
why don’t you try doing something else?
My dad wouldn’t allow it.
I got in
but I couldn’t keep going.
No wonder he’s ashamed of me.
But your dad wasn’t the one studying.
He didn’t know how stressful it was.
His opinion can’t be more important than yours, right?
If you kept pushing
until you reached your limit,
ultimately, it could be worse.
Then…what do you think I should do?
No idea.
What the hell?
Why don’t you open a food stand at my school?
So every morning you can give me a ride.
Or you can do it in front of school.
So after school, you can give me a ride home
I’m such a genius.
Giving you a ride back and forth?
A ride is all you care about?
So you will be in my life forever?
Why?
Can’t I?
Being a teacher is kind of sad, too.
The kids come to school,
study,
take exams,
and then leave.
Only you and I
are still here after decades.
How old are you, huh?
You’re speaking like an old man.
Who are you calling old?
You!
You are old.
I’m not old. Look!
You think an old man like me…
Hey!
Not an old man.
I’m a runner.
You can’t even speak properly.
Why don’t you come and catch me?
Is that a dare?
When are you gonna get up?
I’ll give you five.
Five minutes?
5…4…3…2!
Oh, come on!
Oh, no!
I take it back!
Now, everyone.
I’d like to thank you all
for your dedication on our practice.
Even though someone was…
a bit naughty.
I’ll let that slide.
And where is Zippo?
He passed out.
Passed out?
Okay, so…
Everyone, please have fun.
Just enjoy yourselves!!
Yay!!
Shrimps.
Let’s eat.
I want shrimps, too.
Hey, stop.
Can I have one?
Peel them yourself.
But I’m your best friend.
-Peel them yourself if you wanna eat them.
-Damn.
I’m not used to this.
I never thought you could do something like this.
Well, I’m trying to win you over.
And when I am won?
Then I might want something more.
Here, have a bite.
How is it?
Yum-yum.
You want more?
Why did you take me here?
It’s a date.
A date?
CUSTOMIZED CAPS
399฿ A PAIR
Hey!
Hold on a sec.
A date?
-Let me see.
-So cute.
-You mean the shirt?
-I mean you two.
Oh.
Stop.
Sh*t!
CUSTOMIZED CAPS
Let’s get the caps.
We’re here to pick up the caps
Oh, they’re done.
Do you need a bag?
No, thank you.
Here.
What?
Here it is.
You got the wristband made for me.
So I had this made for you.
Thank you.
-Look, the lions.
-Just as cute as before.
A pair of lions.
Match Point.
Can you draw us, please?
Man Oh, good evening.
Please have a seat.
-Good evening.
Can you get a bit closer?
-Oh, sure.
-Sure.
Can you put your cheeks together?
Our cheeks?
Here.
For me?
I know you like it.
So...
Can I open it now?
This is it.
Sadhu, please be the secret one.
You want it that much, huh?
Here I go?
3…
2…
1…
Sh*t!
Secret!
Do you know that…
Uhh...
Secret one.
It’s the only one…I was missing.
Mmm.
I know that.
Thank you so much.
Do you like it that much
Well…
You don’t get it.
When you…
finally get that one thing you’ve been missing…
The thing that completes you.
Do you know...
how valuable that is?
I meant this art toy.
Mmm.
The art toy.
What’s your type?
Well...
Someone I’m comfortable to be with.
And understands how much tennis
means to me.
What about you?
My type...
is you.
Be serious.
I am.
When I choose someone,
it means they’re the best for me.
Mmm.
I used to imagine
what I would do
if I had a boyfriend.
What do you wanna do?
Yes!
Great!
When you said you wanted to do something
with your boyfriend,
you mean practicing tennis?
So…
if I were your boyfriend,
I’d have to train with you forever?
That would be nice.
I like playing with you.
No one else…
can compare to you.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
Have you ever regretted
giving up tennis because of me?
Not really.
I think…I really like making arts.
Besides,
you made the best of your opportunity.
If I’d continued playing tennis,
I wouldn’t have been as good as you anyway.
You’re talking down on yourself.
I think you still got it.
If you…
want to pursue tennis,
-you can do it.
-Oh, please.
I don’t.
I prefer doing it for fun.
Someone as hotheaded as me
might turn tennis into Muay Thai.
I can imagine that.
Please don’t think you owe me anything.
So...
will you keep finding the time to play tennis with me?
Yes, sir.
Yay!
One more game?
Sure.
You wanna sleep in my room?
Well… I told Petong to sleep in your room instead.
I figured we would be out here so late.
I would also have to go back, take a shower,
turn on the lights and dry my hair.
I didn’t want to disturb Petong.
Did you plan this?
What?
I didn’t plan anything.
I just...don’t want to disturb Petong.
But it’s up to you.
If you don’t want to sleep with me,
that’s fine.
You can go back to your room.
But three people in one room might be a bit crowded.
Fine, I’ll go.
But don’t even think about that thing.
What thing?
I won’t.
But you…
Don’t even think about it.
Go take a shower
and get some rest.
What a day, right?
Is something wrong?
Today has been so wonderful, Bay.
I don’t want it to end
Tomorrow…
when you wake up,
I’ll still be here.
When we go back,
you’ll still see me.
We’ll continue to have wonderful days
like this.
Okay?
But if we really date,
can we still have wonderful days like this?
I’ll have to go to the national camp.
And the problems with our dads…
Don’t you worry.
I really enjoyed today, Bay.
But I don’t see the possibility
that we can really be together.
You know what?
This is how I see it.
if there’s a possibility,
I’ll do anything
to make it possible.
Just trust in me.
I will always support you.
That took more energy than playing tennis.
You’re tired?
Want a boiled egg?
I peeled one for you.
You take such good care of me.
Of course.
Because I’m boyfriend material.
You’re not supposed to say that yourself.
Why don’t you say it then?
Stop eating.
Say it.
Please.
-My tofu.
-My baby.
-Hey, who said you can do that?
-What’s going on with you and Sun?
-Sun!
-Yes?!
-Do you think our dads know about us?
-If my dad finds out,
-I’ll just come out to him.
-Muah!
-Can I call you my boyfriend now?